Hey, what's up? Welcome to the Grow Your
Life podcast. My name is Jeremiah
Kowski. On this podcast, I talk about
ways that coaches, trainers, and mentors
can scale their businesses, make more
money, get more leads, and close more
deals in their business. And that's what
I want to talk about here today is about
closing more sales. You know, I work
with my clients all the time on creating
lead magnets and funnels, and we can
talk about all of that, but one of the
things that I find that often times
people lack is the sales skills required
to be able to sell to people, to get
them to buy from you. You know, in my
wealthy coach academy program, I work
with my clients every single week on
dialing those things in, getting the
results that they want, and turning them
into results for them. And so listen,
I'd love to see you as a part of that.
You can jump in by checking out one of
the links in the description on YouTube
or over on my website. Now, what I want
to talk about is that sales skills is
one of the number one things that's
going to determine whether you are going
to make money or not. And I see way too
many coaches and mentors, they're way
too soft when it comes to selling. They
don't want to be too salesy. And I get
it. You want to help people. You have a
desire to help people. I do, too. If you
look at my content now and I want to
maybe open your paradigm up a little bit
about sales is if you watch my content,
if you listen to my podcast, if you
watch my YouTube videos, if you check
out the webinars that I have, I I
am unashamed about my selling. Like, I'm
selling you something. I have I have my
wealthy coach academy program. It's
amazing. It's incredible. I have my VIP
coaching program. It's even more amazing
and incredible where I work one-on-one
with my clients.
I I don't hold back on that, but I also
provide incredible value. I don't hold
back on the value that I provide. And
so, here's the thing is that if you
don't hold back on the value that you
give people,
selling with confidence, with urgency,
with excitement
is you must do that.
People don't feel like, "Oh, you're just
in it for the sale. Oh, you're just, you
know, like you might have like a small
5% of people that think that." I'm sure
there's 5% of people that might listen
to this podcast and think things like
that. They're probably not going to
listen to this episode. Um, but like the
majority of people, they're like, "Okay,
like I get it. Like Jeremiah's got a
business. He's he's running a business
and he's providing so much value for
free. like I can overlook the fact that
he's advertising and using this as an
advertising tool for all of his coaching
and all of his marketing. So I want to
flip that to you to say your people
provide exceptional value but you need
to also learn to sell and you need to
sell frequently and this has become far
more important I would say in probably
in the last two years than it was
before. Previously, we would like
provide a lot of value to people and
then we would move them into a sales
experience.
And now it's different. It's different
is you want to tell people about what
you have to offer every time that you
are talking. And I'm talking about video
content specifically. I'm talking about
uh emails that you're sending out to
people, the ways that you're connecting
with people once they're on your email
list. Um, once they're in your
ecosystem, like long form video content,
you want to be talking about what you
have for sale. Um, on your Instagram
reels, I don't talk about anything that
I have for sale. I talk about my free
webinars on Instagram reels. My emails,
I will lead people to watch my content,
to consume long form videos like this or
webinars that I have. So, like my
webinars, those are a piece of content.
Like I have a webinar that I'm that I
just launched all about generating
leads. It's called the art of lead
getting. It's over my website
jeremicowsky.comleads.
And
in there like I'm I'm selling my program
to people that you can find in the links
in the description on YouTube. I'm
selling my program. You got to be direct
and explicit
about the fact that you have something
to sell. Not beating around the bush.
not putting your tail between your legs,
hoping that by not selling and providing
so much value that people suddenly
romantically come and look at what you
have to offer.
It doesn't work that way. And that's for
every niche that's out there. That's for
every industry. I don't care what if
you're a therapist, if you're a life
coach, if you are an AI coach, if you
are a service provider,
you have to be selling and you have to
be selling all the time. The purpose of
your leads is to close more sales. Now,
I have two great books that I love on
this topic. Number one, uh Dan Kennedy's
uh direct response marketing book. So
good. Love this one. Um, it's uh the No
BS direct response marketing book. Let
me see if I on the on the YouTube
version of this. If I can pull this up
for you so you can kind of take a look
at this.
Um, no, it's not this one. This one's
the social media one. It's this one
right here.
It's the black and red one. Direct
marketing for non-direct marketing
businesses.
for ser service service provider
businesses for
coaching businesses. This is one of the
best books that's out there. I read this
probably every six months and it uses
proven direct mail strategies
that you can do for online, offline,
viral marketing, all of that. But the
goal is every lead is a potential sale.
So my goal is this is always I want to
get people on my email list. Once
they're on my email list, I want to get
them into my coaching program. Once
they're in my coaching program, I want
to upgrade people into my VIP program.
Okay? And so like I have down here, I
have my content. This is my free
content, but it's always leading to go
to the next level, which is my coaching
program, my wealthy coach academy
program that we have right now that we
that we offer. Once somebody's in the
coaching program, I want to get people
into my VIP program. My VIP program is
currently it's $900 a month. Um,
and it's where I work with you closely
one-on-one. This one's a group coaching
program for 200 bucks a month. This
one's a one-on-one VIP program for 900 a
month. So, like, you can see the value
there, right? Incredible. And that's how
we have a a sustainable sevenfigure
business is we have this we got the free
content provides value to people but
we're always using it to lead people to
that next level that you have. And so
you want to keep that in mind is that
you are you got to be selling and you
got to learn to sell effectively.
There's another great book that's out
there. I just love this. The way of the
wolf by Jordan Belelffort is actually
one of the best most ethical sales books
by a guy who got in trouble for some
very unethical stuff. If you ever watch
the movie The Wolf of Wall Street, it's
all about him. Uh, but this is actually
it's kind of like his way of giving back
to the community is what I feel whenever
I've read it. It's it's literally is the
most honest uh upright high integrity
way of selling that's ever been written
in my opinion and and the most effective
as well. And that's what I love about
this book, The Way of the Wolf. He talks
about how to persuade, how to influence,
how to get people to buy from you in a
way without being super salesy, without
coming across as super salesy because
you don't want to come across that way.
That's in your energy. That's how you
show up. But you want to be confident.
You want to be sharp as attack. These
are all quotes from the book right
there. You want to build trust with
people. You want to raise their trust in
you, your product, your service to a
level 10. And when people trust you,
they will buy what you offer. when they
trust that you're going to be able to
deliver the the result, that your
product is going to be able to deliver a
result, that your service is going to be
able to deliver the result, that you're
going to deliver what you promise to
them. And when people trust you, trust
goes a long way to producing the result
that you're looking for. And it's the
most important thing in business is
building and developing that trust. So,
those two books are really great. Again,
highly recommend. No BS, Direct Response
Marketing. I should probably I should
probably grab the paperback of this one
just so I have it here in my office. Um,
and then The Way of the Wolf by Jordan
Belelffort right here. Sorry, I'm
switching the screen so much.
Highly, highly recommend those books.
And so what it takes is is that you're
going to learn how to sell on video.
You're going to learn how to sell in
your sales copy, in your emails that
you're sending to people. And in my
wealthy coach academy program, that's
what I mentor people on is how to do
that. We've got we got courses, we got
trainings on those. Uh I walk you
through step by step the nuances of it.
A big part of it is getting out of your
own head, getting out of your own way.
Uh getting getting off the sidelines and
into the game where you're connecting
with people. You're making a direct
connection with people. You know,
sometimes as you generate leads, even
reaching out to some of those leads to
figure out what do they desire, what do
they want, and helping guide and direct
them to reach those goals. And so if
you're a coach, if you're a mentor, if
you're a service provider, if you're
somebody who helps other people in some
way and you're generating leads, leads
is only one part of it. Closing sales is
the other part and growing in those
sales skills. Okay? So again, in my
programs, we mentor you on those things.
Those books are honestly going to be
like my number one and number two
resources on getting better at sales,
direct response sales, direct response
marketing, and producing the profits
that you're looking for. Um, if you want
to dive deeper into kind of the nuance
of it, again, I'm I'm going to probably
make some more videos on that here on
this channel, but I wanted to just talk
about that here today is that sales is
important. I see my clients, they
generate leads, but they're not getting
sales. And it's because of a lack of
sales skill. That's all it is. It's that
skill and that ability to have that
sales conversation and to close the deal
and to get the money exchange going and
to get people to give them the kind of
money that they want. And then how do
you automate that? How do you turn it
from onetoone to automating that
process? And that's a big part of it.
That's a huge part of it is being able
to automate that process for you so that
you can connect with people and close
those deals. Listen, we'll talk soon.
Thanks for listening. Grow your life,
everybody. Have a good one.
[Music]
[Applause]